<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Book</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="chapter1">
        When old Mrs. Goose swam by, she gabbled loudly, “How pretty they are!
Except that last one, he’s ugly! You’d better get rid of him, Mrs. Duck.”
“No way! I don’t care if he’s grey; he’s mine! Someday he’ll be pretty,” Mama
Duck said.
The duckling sighed sadly and walked toward the others with his head bent.
He was already too used to hearing such words.
Every time they crossed the yard, all the animals laughed at the duckling,
poking him and teasing him. One day, the duckling couldn’t stand it any
longer, so he headed to the bushes and hid there, knowing that he’d rather
be alone. The duckling was very upset about being so ugly. Every time he
looked at his reflection in the lake, he saw a grey, chubby, ugly duck. He
walked sadly along the lake, when suddenly he came across a family of wild
ducks.
The duckling wanted to join them as they were as gray as he was. They
greeted him warmly, without a thought to the fact that he was ugly. The
duckling became friends with them, and they started to swim around and
take little trips on the lake together.
    </string>
    <string name="chapter2">
        Many years ago, in a city in Arabia, there was a boy called Aladdin. He lived with his mother
        in a little house near the market, and they were very poor. Aladdin’s mother worked all day,
        and sometimes half the night, but Aladdin never helped her.
          He was a lazy boy and he did not like to work. He only wanted to play all the time. Every
        morning he ran through the streets to the market. There, he talked and laughed and played with
        his friends all day. Then in the evening he went home for his dinner.And every night his mother
        said to him: ‘Oh, Aladdin, Aladdin! You are a lazy boy- a good-for-nothing! When are you going to do some work, my son?’
          But Aladdin never listened to his mother.
          One day in the market there was an old man in a long black coat. Aladdin did not see him,
        but the old man watched Aladdin very carefully. After some minutes he went up to an
        orange-seller and asked:
    </string>
    <string name="chapter3">
        Sometimes someone would speak in a boat. But most of the boats were silent except for the
        dip of the oars. They spread apart after they were out of the mouth of the harbour and each
        one headed for the part of the ocean where he hoped to find fish. The old man knew he was
        going far out and he left the smell of the land behind and rowed out into the clean early
        morning smell of the ocean. He saw the phosphorescence of the Gulf weed in the water as he
        rowed over the part of the ocean that the fishermen called the great well because there was
        a sudden deep of seven hundred fathoms where all sorts of fish congregated because of the
        swirl the current made against the steep walls of the floor of the ocean. Here there were
        concentrations of shrimp and bait fish and sometimes schools of squid in the deepest holes
        and these rose close to the surface at night where all the wandering fish fed on them.
    </string>
    <string name="chapter4">
        As soon as Dete had disappeared the old man went back to his bench, and there he remained
        seated, staring on the ground without uttering a sound, while thick curls of smoke floated
        upward from his pipe. Heidi, meanwhile, was enjoying herself in her new surroundings; she
        looked about till she found a shed, built against the hut, where the goats were kept; she
        peeped in, and saw it was empty. She continued her search and presently came to the fir trees
        behind the hut. A strong breeze was blowing through them, and there was a rushing and roaring
        in their topmost branches. Heidi stood still and listened. The sound growing fainter, she
        went on again, to the farther corner of the hut, and so round to where her grandfather was
        sitting. Seeing that he was in exactly the same position as when she left him, she went and
        placed herself in front of the old man, and putting her hands behind her back, stood and
        gazed at him. Her grandfather looked up, and as she continued standing there without moving,
        “What is it you want?” he asked.
    </string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">This is a book containing random excerpts from well-known stories.</string>
</resources>